smartask.com 2013-08-05

# SmartAsk.com | Privacy Policy

We recognize the importance of your privacy and are sympathetic that the protection of your information affects your use of the Internet. We understand that you may be wary with the information you provide to us or the information that is collected on Smartask. With these concerns in mind, we created our Privacy Policy. Read the following policy to understand how your information is being used and what we do to preserve your personal information. If you cannot comply with this policy, please refrain from using Smartask.

### Collected Information

Typically, Smartask collects two types of information: personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information.

  * **Logging in with Smartask-** When you login with Smartask, you gain access to anything Smartask has to offer. To register a login, you must include your name and email address. With this information, we are able to create a unique browsing experience for each user. Logins also improve our customer relationships and can better generate site improvement and features.
  * **Browsing Smartask-** When you browse Smartask, we automatically collect non-personally identifiable information about each user. This includes a user’s IP address, timestamp information, browser type, searches made and pages viewed. This information is not at all linked to your personal information, but rather helps us with analyzing statistical information about Smartask. 
  * **Cookies on Smartask-** To serve the needs of our users better, we have enabled the use of cookies. Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to your hard drive from your browser. Cookies have unique identification numbers that are used to identify your browser. They are used for authentication purposes, storing site preferences and login information. They are not personally identifiable, but you may disable your use of cookies on your browser settings. Disabling them may limit your use of Smartask. 

### Users Submissions

A user submission is anything a user posts on Smartask. This includes comments, questions, answers and feedback left for Smartask itself. User submissions are shown publically. We may log your submission for site improvement and marketing purposes, but will never include your personal information with our records. However to protect yourself, please do not share any information that you wish to remain private.

### Third Parties

Under no circumstances will your information ever be transferred to outside parties by leasing, selling, renting or trading. Third parties that work in tandem with Smartask are expected to abide by our policy and have access to statistical information. The information will never include personal information.

We display third party links, products and advertisements on our site. These sites are not affiliated with Smartask nor do they follow our policies. When you redirect from our site, we are not responsible for the activity and content on these sites.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act

Identity theft is a serious problem and we want to everything in our power to protect the safety of our users. We took the steps necessary with the California Online Privacy Protection Act, also known as the “Shine the Light” law. Under this act, your information will never be given to third parties without your consent.

### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act

Adults have a responsibility to protect children on the internet. We follow the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. Our site is marketed to users over the age of 13 and we will never knowingly collect information from a user under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13 and wish to use Smartask, please ask help from a parent or guardian. Until you have their approval, do not use Smartask.

### Unsubscribe

Your interaction with Smartask is up to user discretion. You may discontinue your communication with Smartask by visiting our[ Unsubscribe page](http://www.smartask.com/unsubscribe/). After you complete your Unsubscribe form, you will be opted out of future mailings, notifications and emails from Smartask.

Any changes to this policy will be made on this page. Please check back often for updates. We would love to hear from you! Any comments, feedback or questions regarding this policy, please visit our Contact Us page.

Property of Announce Media
